TAP version 13
# Subtest: getRandomColor returns a palette value
ok 1 - getRandomColor returns a palette value
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6077
  ...
# Subtest: createDiaryRecord builds diary page structure
ok 2 - createDiaryRecord builds diary page structure
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3934
  ...
# Subtest: createAlbumRecord builds empty photo container
ok 3 - createAlbumRecord builds empty photo container
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.1206
  ...
# Subtest: createVideoRecord keeps title and url
ok 4 - createVideoRecord keeps title and url
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.0992
  ...
1..4
# tests 4
# suites 0
# pass 4
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 84.6656
