TAP version 13
# Subtest: calculateVideoProgress handles valid durations
ok 1 - calculateVideoProgress handles valid durations
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.5315
  ...
# Subtest: calculateVideoProgress returns zero for invalid duration
ok 2 - calculateVideoProgress returns zero for invalid duration
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.0845
  ...
# Subtest: togglePlaybackFlag and toggleMuteFlag invert state
ok 3 - togglePlaybackFlag and toggleMuteFlag invert state
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.0847
  ...
1..3
# tests 3
# suites 0
# pass 3
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 81.2872
